Step 1: wait  [OK]\NThe screen appears to be completely black with no visible UI elements, search box, or any other content. This could be a
Step 2: click (960, 540) [OK]\NThe screen is completely black with no visible UI elements. This could mean the page hasn't loaded yet, or the applicati
Step 3: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which suggests the page may not have loaded yet or there's an issue with the display. Si
Step 4: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which suggests the page may not have loaded yet or there's an issue with the display. Si
Step 5: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which suggests the page has not loaded or there is an issue with the display. Previous a
Step 6: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which indicates the page has not loaded or there is a display issue. I've tried pressing
Step 7: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which suggests the page has not loaded or there is a display issue. I've tried multiple
Step 8: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which indicates that either the page hasn't loaded, the browser is not open, or there's
Step 9: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which indicates that either the page hasn't loaded, the browser is not open, or there's
Step 10: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which indicates that either the page hasn't loaded, the browser is not open, or there's
Step 11: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which indicates that either the page hasn't loaded, the browser is not open, or there's
Step 12: key  [OK]\NThe screen is completely black, which indicates that either the page hasn't loaded, the browser is not open, or there's